# Kristina L. Hall

A: 178 West Prospect Ave. Apt. 8 Pittsburgh, PA 15205
T: (412) 498-8582
E: klh.media09@gmail.com

W: http://kristinalhall.com



#### Background

Skilled front-end website developer with a thirst for knowledge and a very small learning curve who excels when faced with a challenge. Five years of experience in the field, including 2 years of intense training in a technical school while participating in Industry Lead Projects for actual clients. Have worked in a small agency setting with cross-discipline skills of designing, developing, wire framing, and training as well as an agency setting working directly with designers and project managers to plan and execute projects.

#### Experience

#### **Brunner – Visual Developer**

January 2011 – Current

Front-end developer responsible for building websites (front and back end using a Content Management System many times). Also have experience building rich "micro-sites" that have unique user experiences with appealing visuals including animations and interactive pieces. Also responsible for legacy Flash pieces and media buys featuring Flash banner ads. Also have extensive experience building Facebook Pages (apps) and integrating Social Media into websites.

#### Lava New Media, LLC - Website Developer

October 2008 – December 2011

Designed websites for clients, revised website designs, convert design from PSD format to XHTML/CSS and optimized to work in major browsers. Inserted design into in-house Content Management System for easy maintenance. Developed elements to extend and customize CMS on a per client basis. Animated and developed Flash pieces using ActionScript 2.0 and 3.0.

## Pittsburgh Technical Institute – Tutor and Lab Assistant

May 2007 – November 2008

Tutored students to improve their skills in multimedia technologies. Assisted instructors during application demos and helped guide students in completion of lab projects. Helped students become acclimated to their individual schedules.

#### Education

## **Pittsburgh Technical Institute**

October 2006 – October 2008

Concentration: Website Design and Development, Flash Animation, 3D Modeling and Animation, Audio/Video Editing, and Basic Print Design

Programs: Learned the use of Adobe Creative Suite including Photoshop, Illustrator, Dreamweaver, Flash, Premiere, After Effects, Audition, Fireworks, and Director. Learned to model and animate using Autodesk's 3D Studio Max.

#### Skills

Heavy front-end development using CSS/CSS3/Media Queries/LESS, HTML5, JavaScript/jQuery/Ajax, Flash animation using ActionScript 2.0 and 3.0, asp.NET development, asp.NET MVC experience, asp.NET Umbraco CMS development (C#, XSLT, and MVC setups), cakePHP MVC framework experience, Facebook Page app development and Social Media integration, Pinterest Social Media integration, Twitter Social Media integration, heavy browser and device optimization knowledge, Windows 8 JavaScript app development with Live Tiles, iOS HTML5 app development, light WordPress development, PHP-based Silverstripe CMS development.



### Professional References

## **Heather Bell**

Mobile Project Manager American Eagle 77 Hot Metal Street

Pittsburgh, PA 15203 (412) 390-5813

hhorn@ae.com

# **Kyle Zielinksy**

Visual Development Technology Manager B\*Works – Brunner

11 Stanwix Street Pittsburgh, PA 15222 (724) 880-8892

kzielinsky@brunnerworks.com

## John Kramer

Senior Visual Developer BHive Lab – Brunner 11 Stanwix Street Pittsburgh, PA 15222 (412) 322-0297

Kramer@neonhomer.com

## **Rich Haas**

Instructor
Pittsburgh Technical Institute
1111 McKee Road
Oakdale, PA 15071
(412) 809-5202
haas@pti.edu